//use jquery with for loop for questions
var questions =
[
    {
      question: "Your mind is always buzzing with unexplored ideas and plans.",
      answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
      correctAnswer: "2"
  }  ,
  {
    question: "Generally speaking, you rely more on your experience than your imagination.",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "4"
}  ,
{
    question: "You find it easy to stay relaxed and focused even when there is some pressure.",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "1"
}  ,
{
    question: "You rarely do something just out of sheer curiosity..",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "1"
}  ,
{
    question: "People can rarely upset you",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "5"
}  ,
{
    question: "It is often difficult for you to relate to other people’s feelings.",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "2"
}  ,
{
    question: "In a discussion, truth should be more important than people’s sensitivities.",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "3"
}  ,
{
    question: "You rarely get carried away by fantasies and ideas.",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "4"
}  ,
{
    question: "You think that everyone’s views should be respected regardless of whether they are supported by facts or not",
    answers:[1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "3"
}  ,
{
    question: "You feel more energetic after spending time with a group of people..",
    answers: [1,2,3,4,5],
    correctAnswer: "7"
}  ,
  ]
  
  

  $("<p>").text(questions[0].question)

